SANJA MILORADOVIKJ



Junior Front-End Developer

Contact

Home city:

Phone:

Skopje

077 518 525

Email:

sanjamiloradovic@yahoo.com

GitHub:

https://github.com/SanjaMilo

Linked in:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sanja -m-73764136/

MyPortfolio:

https://sanjamiloradovic.netlify.app

Languages

Fluent English Fluent Serbian

Professional summary

Years of experience in field of banking and finance, International foreign currency money transfers and SWIFT transactions, financial accounting and clients acquisition. Highly motivated to constantly develop new skills and grow professionally. So, I choose new career and self-development path with Brainster's programming academy for Front-end web development and looking forward on the new career prospects and challenges.

Skill Highlights

- Successful working in a team environment, as well as independently
- The ability to follow instructions and deliver quality results
- Strong communication skills
- Scrum methodology

- Ability to learn and addopt new technologies
- SWIFT FIN messages
- Web coding languages and technologies (HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP, JAVASCRIPT, jQuery, AJAX, REACT, JSON, DOM, Git)

Education

Front-end developer – BRAINSTER programming academy – 10/2019 to 07/2020, Skopje

Bachelor of Economics - Faculty of Economics, St. Cyril and Methodius University – 2003, Skopje

Financial Management

Experience

TTK Bank - 03/2019 to 09/2019 Banking associate, front officer in the Skopje Branch

Dolare LLC, Skopje office - 12/2017 to 11/2018 **Payment Operations Specialist**

• International correspondent banks money transfers.

GD GRANIT AD Skopje - 10/2014 to 12/2017 **Financial associate in the Accounting department, Head office**

 Foreign currency payments, bank guarantees, letters of credit, foreign currency accounting.

Hobbies and interests

Mountain and road cycling Distance running Mountain hiking Photography Aikido

Seminars

Mobile Marketing & Analytics held by Crazy labs -12/2019

SWIFT Training – MT 202 COV Messages - Standards Release Seminar (Belgrade, Serbia) – 09/2009

ProCredit Bank AD Skopje - 05/2004 to 04/2013 Client advisor – front officer in Skopje Branch and Business center

• Corporate clients acquisition, Bank's products promotion and customer care and front-office operations.

International payments specialist, Head office

SWIFT specialist for International money transfer messaging

MAT – Macedonian Airlines, Skopje - 08/2000 to 02/2004 Flight attendant

• First working experience during my university studies. Great for building work ethics and professionalism